Joe Rogan podcast. Check it out.
>> The Joe Rogan Experience.
>> TRAIN BY DAY. JOE ROGAN PODCAST BY
NIGHT. All day.
>> All right, bro. David, what's up?
>> Thanks for having me back on. Yeah,
>> my pleasure.
>> Yeah.
>> Well, you're the one that's closest to
the flame, so tell me what's going on.
>> Oh, I know, right? So, uh, living a
nightmare is what I tell my friends. So,
it's definitely um been a tough several
years or so. And uh you know last time
we were on uh just testified in front of
Congress and uh the UAP Disclosure Act
of 23 was you know possibly getting
passed. It failed to get passed and then
I um based on you know things I know
about the Biden administration, things I
heard from the White House, I decided to
kind of lay low for a year. So 24 I
didn't do too much. And then uh
Representative Burlson had this crazy
idea to to hire me as a professional
staff member for Congress working for
him. Uh turns out I guess I was like the
first guy that ever testified in front
of Congress as a whistleblower and then
being subsequently hired by Congress. Um
I was the first guy to ever do that
which is very interesting and very cool.
And I I do thank Burlson for um you know
his leadership on that. And so I did
that for about a year and a half. um
just finished up actually. I was like,
you know what? I'm staying longer than I
thought. You know, I'm going to wait
until Labor Day, see where things are. I
worked pretty hard over uh uh summer
recess in August and and decided uh to,
you know, wind down some of my
activities because I accomplished a lot
of my objectives. We can get into that
obviously and then uh kind of move into
I'll call it my next phase of
operations, which includes a little
break for me. Um it's been very tiring.
I've been kind of, you know, going full
throttle for the last couple years and
whatnot. And so we're really at a, I
think, a poignant moment in US history
with what Trump's done and the things
you've seen in the media and whatnot.
And there's a lot of other stuff
happening behind the scenes because, you
know, a lot of my work has been private
behind the scenes, you know, working for
Congress, specifically Representative
Burlson.
>> So, let me ask you the environment. So,
are there some people in Congress that
are interested in disclosure of this
stuff and pursue you and want to find
out information and want you to tell
them what what's going on and and then
are there other people that are
resisting this? Yeah, I think there's a
big bifurcation of the non-believers and
then kind of the UAP caucus. Although
you see more and more people kind of
signing on to the cause like I did a
presser back in June in front of the
capital with members and we even had
Brigider General retired uh
representative Scott Perry there who was
on the House Intelligence Committee from
my home state of PA and it was good to
see other members, you know, start
showing that they support the cause. But
it has been challenging behind the
scenes and I had many skiff classified
meetings with the members kind of going
over the topological history of this
topic and and some of the deeper darker
kind of you know criminal stuff I bumped
into and how I worked with DOJ to kind
of highlight some of that stuff and
that's what
>> kind of criminal stuff.
>> Yeah. So, uh, when I was, um, looking
into this, and I have to be very
respectful of, uh, my participation in
this because it's an ongoing thing with
DOJ. Um, I was, you know, following the
money, bumping into other activities.
Um, very much like, actually, it's sort
of related. And if you saw in the news
that David Rush, very similar name to
me, it's kind of uh, freaky, uh, but he
was arrested with $40 million of gold
bars. He was a CIA officer. where he
made a fake uh continuity of government
special access program and you know he
went under the radar basically um doing
his own thing and getting gold and
Rolexes and stuff and the FBI raided his
house back in May. True true story.
Yeah, the guy has a
>> is that gold bars?
>> He has he had $40 million of gold bars.
>> Where did he get the gold bars
>> from the agency?
>> They have them laying around.
>> Yeah. I can't get into all the details
of why the government
>> Hold on. The government has gold bars.
>> Yeah. And this guy just snatched him.
>> Yeah. He made I don't know all the
details, but he made a fake continuity
of government special access program
that nobody was briefed into. He like,
you know, papered it and uh nobody at
the CIA questioned what he was doing.
And he was like, "Well, I need, you
know, 40 million in gold bars because of
the special continuity of government
activity."
>> Wait, wait, wait. So that's how they
fund some things in gold bars.
It's almost like uh in Afghanistan when
I was over there, I'd have guys with
briefcases full of $100,000 in cash cuz
you have to pay for things, right?
>> So,
>> but that kind of makes more sense to me
than lugging around gold.
>> Yeah.
>> What does like 40 million in gold bars
look like?
>> Uh I saw the seizure photos. It's a lot.
I mean, it's really
>> Can I see what that looks like?
>> It's approximately 303 gold bars that
each weigh approximately 1 kilogram a
piece.
>> Yo, that's a lot of weight. Yeah, I was
looking for a picture. There's only like
AI photos of it
>> at least that I could find.
>> So, a kilogram is 1.2.2 lb.
>> Yeah. 2.28 or something.
>> That's crazy.
>> 600.
>> He's got 600 lb of gold.
>> Yeah.
>> Where the do you put? So, he just
had it in his house.
>> He did have it at his house and he
laying around.
>> Bunch of Rolexes and all that. And
>> Oh, so he was just going crazy.
>> Yeah. Well, who knows what he was really
going to use the gold for, but that
that's an open-ended thing. And he was
he was pretending that he was using it
for some disclosure type deal or did it
have anything to do with UAPs?
>> Uh not that I'm aware of, but that same
ecosystem I bumped into. So his
fabricated program was a continuity
government program. So that's like, you
know, if something bad happens,
>> people are going to a hideout site, you
know, sanitized location,
>> right?
>> And so what I bumped into unfortunately
was like the deep underbelly of the
federal government. We can get into it.
It's it's a lot of stuff I've never
talked about because it's just very
terrifying and I you know I've been
through a lot of a lot of crazy and
I ended up bumping into a criminal
enterprise uh run out of a particular
agency and um it was basically um
getting money through certain criminal
endeavors the most unspeakable type of
criminal endeavors under the cover of uh
certain national security programs.
That's about as
>> When you say certain unspeakable
>> Yeah.
>> You mean like what do you mean like
trafficking?
>> Yeah.
>> Like child trafficking.
So the government was involved in child
trafficking for money.
>> Officers of the government. That's true.
Yeah. It's it's up. I uh I
briefed members in a classified setting
all the details. Um, and I I'm
highlighting that because
this is how serious this issue is is
there's an ecosystem and there's a lot
of good people are on these programs in
terms of the the UAP side. Yeah. And I
know a lot of them. They're friends of
mine. They're patriotic people doing
their duty, but there is like a small
little cast system of characters um that
are part of this larger ecosystem of uh
no holds barred. we're going to do what
we want and you know we're going to do
whatever kind of criminal activity to
get a washed money uh for our cutouts
like so a good example of course would
be Iran Contra right which is very
famous 86 and the CIA was engaged in
those kind of activities and this has
all been exposed all over north and all
that to fund the contras weapons
purchases procurement etc and a lot of
that you know seemed to uh possibly be
drug trafficking the government never
confirmed that but you look at Barry
Seal and and his um uh statements in the
80s and 90s and and it's likely that
that um probably occurred, you know.
>> Yeah. It was all through Freeway Ricky
Ross.
>> Yeah, that's right.
>> Yeah. Ricky's been on the podcast
multiple times.
>> That's right. That's right.
>> Yeah. He was on what is it like two
years ago, year and a half ago. Last
time he was on. Um
>> it's funny cuz he's out now. Uh became
an attorney while I was in jail. Found
out learned to read first. Okay.
Couldn't read. became an attorney in
jail, found out that they tried him. You
know that triple jeopardy, three strikes
thing.
>> Yeah.
>> They tried him incorrectly. They used
that incorrectly because it's supposed
to be three different times you were
arrested instead of like three crimes
that were attached to one arrest. So, he
gets out of jail. Now, he sells legal
weed.
>> All right. All right.
>> Lovely guy. But he he's a great guy, but
he had no idea that he was selling
cocaine to fund the Contra versus the
Sandinistas.
>> Interesting. He had no idea. He thought
that he was just a a slick character
that just knew what he was doing and
was, you know, he didn't realize that
the CIA was literally allowing him to do
it. Then we've also had Michael Roupert
on the podcast. You know who he is?
>> No.
>> Michael Roupert was the LA narcotics
officer that on uh I believe it was on
C-SPAN. He went on C-SPAN during a
hearing and he exposed the entire or
organization selling drugs in South
Central Los Angeles because he was
involved in it. He was involved in like
busting people that were doing it and
then they told him he has to leave it
alone because it was the CIA.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And so when I bumped into
that stuff, you know, I immediately
worked at Department of Justice.
>> That's one level, but like child
trafficking is another level.
>> I know, man. It's it's really up
and and there's a lot of details that
are I have a lot more questions than
answers and and I you know I worked with
the OJ and you know from what I
understand uh I got a gold star in a
brief to Cash Patel about it last year.
I wasn't in the briefing, but I, you
know, I I was told I got kudos, but it
was very disturbing. And so, like,
obviously, a lot of these programs are
legal in the sense that there's in terms
of UAP stuff, there's, you know,
classified executive orders back in the
day that covers them and
>> and they're upstanding citizens and we
could we could litigate like, you know,
uh, Congress wasn't necessarily brought
into the fold enough from an oversight
perspective, etc. But, you know, the
core of the program, you know, does have
uh a legal beginning, but when you don't
have oversight, unfortunately, certain
small pockets of people start doing
that they shouldn't have. And I and
unfortunately,
>> I got deeply ins snared in that. There
was a very small group of people that
uh, you know, pushed me over the edge
and I had to do what I got to do to to
you know, protect myself. And I never
wanted to be a whistleblower. You know,
I was a deeply entrenched, you know,
15-year intel officer, military officer
in the Air Force. You know, I was
working some of the country's most
sensitive issues. You know, started
going to the White House to brief the
National Security Council in my mid20s
on space issues back during the Obama
administration. And and in 2019 when I
joined the UAP task force and I was
tasked to investigate this, I was like,
"Sure, I'll look into it." you know, the
special access program or black program
community has a lot of dysfunction and
and maybe some stuff wasn't reported,
you know, you know, correctly and and I
didn't know really what I was going to
find, but if there was a US program, you
know, I'd figure it out. I'd probably
get cleared to it and we'd be fine. We'd
have like a mafia meeting and and uh you
know that and I know why it was
protected the way it is and whatnot. But
unfortunately
about a year and a half about October
2020 is when kind of my life changed and
particular individuals instead of coming
to me who knew me by the way personally
I know I know them personally now Dave
you're bumping into something you know
I'm going to defensively brief you this
is what it is or hey I'm going to slide
an NDA sign this and I'll read you in
and my colleagues and I joked about that
like we're bumping in the
eventually somebody's going to knock on
my door in my office and be like, "Hey,
I need to talk to you." And
unfortunately, that never happens. Um,
it's really tragic because that would
have been an easier way. But, um, I
immediately got administratively nuked